After a comprehensive evaluation,
your performance does not meet the
company's development requirements.
The company has decided to negotiate
the termination of your contract.
What the hell?
What else can you do
besides pissing me off all day?
People nowadays are too fragile.
You can't even handle this little thing.
Let's give the promotion quota
to someone else this time.
What's wrong with young people
taking a little loss?
Didn't you volunteer for it?
Do you have a brain or not?
Did I force you?
Who are you showing that long face to?
Nobody will want you if you leave here.
Doing a good job is
what you're supposed to do.
Give first before talking about returns.
Why are you so special?
I'm doing this for your own good.
There are no unachievable goals.
No matter how hard it is,
Mom and Dad will buy you
an apartment in the city.
Is the client looking at you
or the proposal?
Can you at least pretend a little better?
Why wasn't it completed?
The key performance indicators
this time...
You can't even take this little grievance?
You can't even handle this little thing.
We can't hit innocent people.
Why should wage slaves
make things hard for each other?
I shouldn't add to
the cleaning lady's workload.
Tangtang,
I've heard you resigned.
I've been sick of
that crappy company for a long time.
The 996 schedule, exploiting people,
and shifting the blame.
It's a good thing you left.
News travels so fast.
That manager Hu
said you were incompetent.
He just wanted an excuse to fire you
and
make room for his newly graduated niece.
Forget it. I'm tired.
I can't hustle anymore.
Ever since graduation,
I've been working mechanically every day,
only to go home and work more overtime.
I don't even know
what the meaning of life is anymore.
I used to believe that hard work pays off.
But now I realize
hard work is just the ticket.
Winning still depends on luck.
I used to have expectations too.
But every expectation in life
just ends up destroying me.
My bestie would never say something
so poetic and depressing.
I don't care who you are.
Get out of my bestie's body right now.
Back off! Back off! Back off!
I can't explain it to you. I'm hanging up.
Wait, wait, wait.
I know you're in a bad mood right now,
but please don't
psych yourself out.
Do you remember?
I opened a youth retirement home
called Yunbianshang
by the sea of clouds
in Xiayanbei, Xinchang.
I have to go on a long business trip
for a few days.
Can you come over
and help me look after it?
Open the window of my place,
and there's the sea of clouds.
Behind it is a tea plantation.
You can water flowers
and brew tea every day,
and lie in the yard
counting stars at night.
How romantic!
The feng shui in Xiayanbei, Xinchang
is nourishing.
You definitely won't wither away here.
If I could rest in peace
in a heavenly place like that,
not bothering anyone,
just quietly becoming nutrients
for the mountains...
that sounds pretty nice.
Okay, send me the address.
Tang Jialing has really made it.
She opened a nursing home
and can even afford
such an imposing security team.
Hold on a second.
Hello.
Listen, lady,
we're debt collectors.
Please, guys.
Have some mercy.
Give me a little more time.
I'm a bit tight on cash lately.
In a month,
I promise to wire the money
to your accounts.
This is your friend, right?
Listen to me, pay up right now.
If you don't, I'll take her--
No, no, bro.
It has nothing to do with me.
I'm just here to retire.
You're so young, and you're retiring?
Who are you kidding?
Do you think I'd believe that?
Wait a minute.
Aren't I here to seek death?
What am I afraid of?
Believe it or not.
I have no money, but you can take my life.
Come on. Kill me for the debt.
Come on!
Take out your knives and axes
and hack at my head.
Come on, chop right here.
Don't hold back.
Please just kill me,
okay?
Are you trying
to scam us?
We live in a civilized society.
You have to obey the law, right?
We're collecting debts legally.
We don't do that mafia stuff.
You just need a month,
right?
One month it is.
Let's go, let's go.
What a freak.
Let's go.
Sir, don't run!
I can sign a waiver.
I really have no other choice right now.
Can you just give me one more month?
Don't worry.
I'm already raising funds
on Wall Street.
Once I get the money,
I'll come back to save you right away.
It's all my damn ex-boyfriend's fault.
He insisted on borrowing money.
He claimed he wanted
to expand the nursing home,
and secretly borrowed it under my name.
In the end, the jerk ran off,
and the debt can't be paid.
Isn't this
your favorite dress?
Your boyfriend, Zhang Yi,
thought this gown was
too expensive back then.
He said you should just rent it for a day.
I've already bought it.
That's the spirit.
We independent women get what we want.
Does Zhang Yi
know you lost your job?
If his family finds out,
they'll flip out.
The moment I lost my job,
I also lost my relationship.
Why didn't you meet
the KPI this time?
Answer me.
Eight million
was an impossible target to begin with.
There are no impossible targets.
Pack your things and leave right now.
Isn't this
the highlighter you've been saving?
You actually used it today.
Living like there's no tomorrow?
I rarely use it,
so there's still a lot left.
Forget it.
I'll just mix it with my ashes.
I'm gonna be the most dazzling person
in the underworld.
You're hilarious, sis.
Honestly, where are you going
dressed up like this?
A date?
I'm going to die.
You're as funny as ever.
Oh my god.
My phone.
Give it to me.
This is so nice.
The tea garden smells so good.
Qingqing,
why did you send us so much money?
Your mom and I have enough.
We took on another part-time job
to buy you a new house
before you get married.
My parents already know you got fired.
You're an outsider.
They didn't want us together
in the first place.
And now you've lost your job.
They're forcing me to break up with you.
Let's stop contacting each other for now.
We'll talk when you find a new job.
Why did you unfollow me?
Did I do something wrong?
Do you like someone else?
You're my only fan.
The annual blame-shifting conference
is on again.
As a corporate slave
in a big tech company,
I can only slack off and watch the drama.
I'm not taking the blame for this.
How can you blame us for this?
Our budget is already
much higher than our peers'.
It's obviously your proposal
that has problems.
Customers don't even have the desire
to click on it.
What's going on?
Who is it?
So arrogant. What is this?
Watching this kind of video in the office?
Someone must have connected
to the wrong computer.
What on earth is this?
Who's watching this?
Who?
Who is this?
How can they watch this kind of stuff
in the office?
Whenever I feel exhausted,
your videos always give me strength.
It's a pity I didn't get to see
you become a big star,
but thank you for being with me
through this time.
I'll continue to support you
in my next life.
Peace and quiet at last.
Is this your phone?
Yes, it is.
Thank you so much.
It just hit me.
I'm sorry. I didn't mean to.
I just found this phone too annoying,
so I tossed it,
and...
What are you doing lying here?
I saw this place is backed by mountains
and faces the water.
It's beautiful,
clearly a great feng shui spot.
So,
I want to rest in peace here.
This is my family's tea garden.
I'm sorry.
If you mind,
I can find another place.
You can't do it anywhere.
We're about to be evaluated
as a provincial beautiful village
demonstration site.
You can't commit suicide
anywhere around here.
Why are there KPIs everywhere?
I'll leave then.
I won't cause you any trouble.
You don't know me.
Should we know each other?
It's fine.
We can get to know each other now.
Hello, I'm Yun Qingqing.
Yun Qingqing,
I'll be keeping an eye on you.
Don't even think about
dying in front of me.
Gu Hai
Shi Zheng
Zhu Zifo
Zhang Yanyan
He Lijian
Liu Chengcheng
Chang Zhicheng
Li Jiakang
Zhao Xinran
Xin Xiaoqing
Zhang Xiaojie
Wu Changling
Zhong Shangyu
Sui Yugang
Sun Wenyan
He Cuiyan
You Weiyun
Han Bing
Yang Yunshu
Zhang Yue
Zhang Luyao